I know what I'm supposed
to do to Don't let
Fight for the way
If you want to open the door,
you'll be able to open the door.
Let's start with the new world.
Look, look, look!
I've been waiting for a few years.
I've been waiting
for a
long time.
You don't forget to fight together.
I don't have no problem.
I don't have to kill you.
I don't have to know how far.
The light has gone?
I
don't
know how far.
I've reached my heart.
We'll fight together.
The path that led Luffy to
Marineford began long ago.
Ten years ago, in fact, in the East Blue.
There lies a small town known as Windmill
Village, where people lived quiet,
peaceful lives.
But it was the nearby Mount Grove
where few would dare to set foot.
For only the strong could
survive in its dark woods,
faced with beasts that would
make quick work of trespassers.
What's wrong with being king
of the pirates, Grandpa?
The pirates are cool.
And what makes you think I care?
I'm gonna slap you.
Eating that Devil Fruit
wasn't enough trouble for you?
Now this nonsense, you and your big brother
Ace are going to become fine marines.
You understand me?
Ow, ow, ow, you suck!
I thought I was supposed to
be made out of rubber now!
Why does this still hurt so much?
I thought leaving you in a nice
village would keep you safe,
but pirates won't be satisfied until they
get their grubby hands on everything!
What's this do?
Hey, shut the hell up!
Whatever it is you're
selling, I don't want knives!
Put it on!
Garp, what are you doing here?
Charming as ever.
Sorry for the cold welcome,
but I hope you don't have another
ridiculous favor to ask us.
You realize Ace is already ten, right?
Oh, is he now?
And how's the little scam doing?
Good?
Well, there's a handful, of course.
And we've been watching over
the brat for long enough.
So just take him away.
Never mind.
Yeah, that's the problem.
We do mine.
Speaking of brat, would
you shut that one up?
He's yours now.
Hey, Luffy, tell him
hello. Yo! Wait a sec.
Who is he?
He's my grandson.
I never heard about this.
And you want us to take
care of the little monster.
A little darling, I mean.
Well, no way. Fine.
Then I'll give you two choices.
You can either raise my grandson
or spend your life in prison.
Pretty generous, considering
all the crimes you've committed.
No fair.
The thing is, I'd rather
stay out of the slammer.
Frankly, if you ask me that
on one of Ace's bad days,
I might have to go for the
prison option after all.
And two breaths?
Yeah, I don't think so.
This kid looks like a real charmer, too.
Like your face?
You wanna fight, you
little punk? Hehehehe!
Daddy!
Don't let him get to you!
Huh?
Ew! Spit! That's gross!
Who did that?
Hey! You jerk!
You better apologize for
that! Hey! There he is!
Oh, hello Ace! Welcome back!
I'm waiting!
Luffy, this here is Ace.
He's three years older than you.
Anyway, you're going to be living
with him and Dadan from now on.
What?
Not so fast!
You play nice. Ace, techno!
You'll do it.
Sir, as you wish, sir!
It's your turn to do this.
Old man, can I have some more?
I'm a woman, thank you very much.
Do you even know where you are
right now, you filthy little urchin?
No.
Okay, then I'll tell you.
This is the den of the Dadan family.
Mountain bandits that rule Mount Grove.
Mountain bandits?
Ball, mountain bandits are lame.
Well, you're stuck with us.
Or rather, we're stuck with you thanks
to that pushy grandfather of yours.
But if you don't want to
stay, that's fine by me.
Hey, go get eaten by a bunch
of wolves for all I care.
Easy, boss, easy.
I just wanted some more rice.
Meat would be nice.
In case you didn't notice, all this meat
came from that bison ace brought back.
Even though he's a kid like you,
he has to work to earn his cape.
The bandit's life's a hardwood boy.
Tomorrow, you're gonna pay
in blood, sweat, and tears.
Cleaning, doing laundry,
polishing our boots and weapons,
robbery, fraud, murder, and terror!
And if you go crying to
your dear old grandpa,
we'll string you up
without a second thought.
One bowl of rice and one glass of
water, that's all I can promise you.
The rest you get for yourself.
You're gonna have to
grow up real fast, kid,
or you're gonna go hungry
before the week's up.
No problem. No problem?
Not crying and begging for mercy?
Grandpa threw me in the jungle one time,
so I know how to tough it out just fine.
There's plenty of water to drink,
and I can eat frogs and snakes and
mushrooms and stuff all I want.
I'm gonna be a pirate someday,
so we gotta be strong.
This is gonna be real fun.
Boss! You okay?
Hurry, help her up!
Keep home!
Why's he leaving?
One more!
Hey, get back here, you!
Hold on, what do you mean
you're gonna be a pirate?
AND STOP IGNORING ME!
HEYYY!
He just got here and he's already a pain!
It's gonna be like having
a baby Garp living with us!
No, no, it's okay.
Hey!
Wait for me!
Hi!
My name's Luffy!
Everything's cool now!
I'm not mad about you spitting on me!
Why are you all laughing?
But the guy just spilled some booze on me.
It's not worth getting bent out of shape.
I'd rather be friends.
So can I come with you?
It's a dinner!
Meow!
I don't know what to do.
Ace is back!
You know what that means! Boom!
Huh?
Wait, you're alone?
That's not good.
Uh, yeah.
Where's Luffy?
Was it he with you? Beats me.
Get a hold of yourself this
is serious no biggie oh
what is that what you're
gonna say to garp when he
finds out we let his
grandson die why do you care
one less crappy brat in the
world you know what while
we're at it screw ace
two if he dies we'll tell
garp it was an accident i
mean that'd be the truth
wouldn't it the devil's
children have the devil's luck
how about that Cause Ace is
the devil's son for sure.
What do you think the government
would do if they found out about him?
Ha!
I'll take my chances with Garp.
Hey, you don't mean that, boss.
Come on, that's the booze talking.
Just sleep it off.
One week later.
Boss, wake up!
Come here, quick!
What?
It's you!
The little bugger isn't dead after all.
You're alive
Why'd you scare us like that, huh?
Easy, easy, boss Where the hell
were you and what were you doing?
Now, now, just give him a second?
He'll answer without
all the face stretching!
I was stuck in the bottom of the valley.
Getting chased by wolves?
Are you nuts?
What the heck were you
trying to do down there?
Well, whatever It's
good you came back safe.
There's nothing good about it!
Another useless mouth to feed.
Get some sleep while you can.
We're putting you to work
bright and early tomorrow.
Hey, Ace!
You going somewhere fun today? Take me!
I know I was gone for a while,
But I still want to be friends!
Wait!
Boss, he's running after Ace again!
Hey!
Get back here!
You still have chores to do!
I'm outta here!
I am gonna wring your
rotten neck, you twerp!
Easy!
You shut your yapper
and go bring him back!
Yes, ma 'am! Hey!
It was the same thing every time.
But that didn't deter him one bit. Ace!
A month passed, two months.
Wait up!
In the rain or in the wind.
Let's make friends!
Ace would run and Luffy would chase him.
Come back!
I'm not giving up yet!
I'm having a tough time losing
him today, stubborn punk.
Uh-oh.
Crap.
This sucks.
Got away again.
How'd he get so darn fast?
Hey, there you are!
That's got to be the nastiest
monster in the forest.
Even I can't beat that thing.
Run away, stupid.
It's going to eat you.
I want to run away, but my
legs won't let me. Damn it.
Ah-ha-ha!
Hm... Ah
-ha
-ha!
Ah!
Ah...
Ah-ha-ha! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Three months had passed, and although
he was covered with cuts and bruises,
Luffy did not relish.
It's the end of the forest.
What is this place?
On the north side of Mount Grove,
not far from where Dedan's bandits live,
there is a surprise at
the end of the forest.
Covered in a thick mist, piles of
trash reach toward the heavens.
It is a place where the unwanted gather.
That goes for the refuse, as
well as those who reside there.
Rogues cast out by society.
It is a den of lawlessness.
Crime and disease run rampant.
With neither marines nor doctors present.
This place is known as Gray Terminal.
Just a bunch of junk.
Gotta be something.
Come on!
Ah!
Ha!
Finally!
Torque it over!
Yeah, right!
That's mine!
Screw you!
I found it!
You're gonna break it, you idiots!
That's cool, man!
I just wanna cash it in for you!
Yeah, right!
Come on, just give me one pearl!
Back off!
You can only blame yourself.
Next time, let's try this
without all the running.
Look what I found!
No way!
Get back here!
Thief!
Hey!
Move it, you brat!
What is your problem?
You want some of this?
He went that way!
Samo!
Hey, are you up there?
Oh, what's up, Ace?
Sorry, I'm a little late this time.
More than a little.
I went out there and made
a killing already today.
Oh, yeah?
Well, maybe I did, too. Let's see.
Whoa, dude!
You got more than me!
That's a ton of cash. What happened?
Some chumps near the gate, robbed
them blind and made a run for it.
Well, crap.
Guess you win again, buddy.
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
We've got five years of
pirate savings piled up.
We should both be happy about that.
We worked pretty hard.
Yeah, no kidding.
We'll leave this stump behind and go
places these chumps never even dreamed of.
This is all gonna be
worth it. Just you wait.
We'd better put it away now.
We can't let anyone else see this.
So how much is a ship?
I want a good one, but it
seems like we're pretty rich.
Yeah, could take ten million.
Maybe even more.
Shouldn't rush it.
Did you say ship?
You're gonna be pirates?
And you've got hidden treasure already?
I'm gonna be a pirate too!
Shut up!
Know what's cool?
Now that I know where you go,
I can follow you every day!
Great!
Luffy, huh?
This is the brat you were talking about.
Does that mean you told
your friends about me?
I was telling my friend
how annoying you were.
He also told me that your
head's full of rocks.
Head rocks!
You do realize we're messing
with you here, right?
The route I took here
wasn't easy to follow.
I knew he was hard-headed, but
I didn't think he was so tough.
So great that Ace has other friends, too!
I bet we're all gonna be best pals!
I'm not your pal.
You don't even know my name, stupid.
Okay, then what is your name?
It's, uh, a secret.
I told you, didn't I?
You need to live here.
The mountains made you tough, but at this
rate, our whole plan's gonna be ruined.
What now?
He knows our secret.
We can't trust him to keep his mouth shut.
He's too stupid.
We'll kill him.
Yep, sounds good.
Stop, this is scary!
Somebody help me!
I don't want to die!
Give me a break, this kid is the worst!
Just kill him already, hurry it up!
He's your problem, what are you doing?
Because I've never killed
anyone before, okay?
Well, neither have I!
I don't know how this crap works!
Just don't throw me in the
water, I'm begging you!
Okay, the river!
That's convenient, but
why did he say that?
I told you, he's stupid!
Somebody help me!
That's enough!
Don't kill me!
Wait, listen.
I just heard some screaming.
Son of a kid! Ah, damn it!
Somebody hurt him! Set him free.
We gotta get out of here and fast.
If people start snooping around,
they'll find our treasure.
Sounds like you're talking
about Ace and Sabo.
Those two are infamous around here.
And the one who took your money.
That was Ace, right?
The kid who had the black hair, you said?
Uh-huh.
This is real pathetic, I know.
We both got sloppy.
He's either cocky or dumb.
You can't rob pirates blind
and expect to get away with it.
Bottom line is, if we
don't get that money back?
Captain Blue Jam's gonna skin us alive!
and I mean literally.
Blue Jam? Crap!
How was I supposed to know
they were working with him?
You robbed those guys?
Are you trying to get us killed or what?
Yeah, this is not gonna end well.
That sword looks sharp, though
you probably saw that already.
The guy with him is porching me.
He's crazy.
Lose a fight with him, and he'll scalp
you alive just to hear you scream.
Just lay low and let him pass by for now.
Uh-oh, he's gone.
You better put me down right now, you
big - How did you get caught already?
Who the hell is this?
This guy won't put me down!
Ace, help!
Ace, why aren't you saving me?
We're friends, right?
We should have killed him.
No, we're all dead. Help!
So, you know Ace, do you?
Yeah, that's right.
And if you cry, do you
think he'll come for you?
Yeah, because we're friends.
Except he just tried to
kill me, so maybe not.
Shut up.
Are you kidding me?
If he's your friend,
maybe you can help us.
See, Ace stole our money.
And if we got it back, we
wouldn't have to hurt anybody.
You don't happen to know
where it is, do you?
We're screwed.
They're gonna take our treasure
for sure for once in your life.
Please shut up
What a crappy lawyer?
All right fine, I'm sure you just forgot.
Don't worry, I have ways
of jogging your memory.
I told you, I don't know!
Let go of me, you dumb jerk!
He's gonna kick your
butt, I'm telling you!
You're a big jerk!
Okay, so now what?
Stop asking me, you know what!
Let me go! No!
I'm not telling you a dark thing!
You little punk!
The Gum-Gum fruit turned me into rubber,
so that stuff's not going to work on me.
Calm down.
A Devil Fruit, huh?
Hmm.
I know how to deal with that.
Bring me my pair of gloves.
Yes, sir!
Hurry, man! Faster!
We're screwed if those guys come back!
We gotta move all this,
but I don't know where.
Luffy's pretty stubborn, but it's only
a matter of time before he rats us out.
I'm not losing our pirate savings
to those jerks or anyone else.
It took us five years to score all this.
We can't get stuck in this dump forever
I'll try to clear this up a little the
money a stole isn't just some chump
change It's a matter of life and death
for me and all of my buddies here,
and you're gonna tell me where it is
Even if I gotta beat it out of you
Well not
That's rough.
I'm warning you, kid.
You don't piss off a pirate.
If I don't kick your ass, Captain Blue
Jam's gonna kill you and all of us, too.
Let me go!
You're hurting me!
Somebody help!
We don't have time to
stand around, you idiots.
Go look for Ace and Sabo
while I take care of this one.
Yes, sir!
Ace and Sabo, huh?
Yeah, I know him.
Oh, I get it.
You're from the city.
Leave those two be.
If you were locals, you'd understand.
They may be kids, but they're also crazy.
Yeah, man, they got claws like
a tiger if you cross them.
A sensabo, huh?
I wouldn't know.
But while we're all
having this little chat,
why don't you always
fork over your wallets?
We don't want any trouble.
We'll ask someone else.
Didn't realize it was getting so late.
All right, I finally did it!
Not even Luffy knows about this spot!
I'm back!
I moved everything. What happened?
Are they poking around at the old place?
No, that's the thing.
Blue Jam's guys are
still out looking for us!
And what does that mean?
I'm telling you, it's Luffy!
All that time and he
still didn't rat us out!
I thought he would since he's
such an idiot that Andy was
crying whenever we left him
But you know what this means,
don't you?
They're torturing him right now
What if he still doesn't talk
Getting awful late, isn't it?
Who did I leave in charge today?
Well, Captain Blue Jam, if I
recall, it should be Porchemy.
Huh, then he'd better hurry.
Well, surely they made the sale.
It couldn't have taken him that long.
Maybe Porchemy thinks he's clever
enough to take my money and skip town.
Of course not, Captain.
I doubt he would throw his life
away over some measly treasure.
Let's hope not.
Come on, kid.
Spit it out.
Wait. Wait.
Portrume, stop it.
I don't think he's going to talk.
He's shutting down.
The kid's not even
calling for help anymore.
If he wasn't going to talk,
he would have done it already.
And to be honest, this is
getting kind of hard to watch.
Show the little bastards some mercy!
If you have time to bitch about this,
then you have time to go look for Ace!
We're the ones who are gonna get
killed here, not the damn kid!
Save your breath,
cause you'll be begging for mercy
from Captain Blue Jam soon enough!
They're gonna kill that child.
Do you think we should call
the sheriff from the city?
There's no point.
I mean, this place doesn't
fall under any country's laws.
Plus, that portrait me guy's a
member of the Blue Jam Pirates.
They're paying off the nobles, you know.
So in other words, even if they
do get arrested for a crime,
they're just gonna be pardoned in the end.
Besides, what's one more dead
body in a place like this?
Nobody gives a damn.
Answer me!
I'm not talking.
You little punk!
I'll beat that secret out of
you or I'll beat you dead!
Tell me!
I won't do it!
I won't talk!
Just let me go!
I'm not telling you!
Fine.
Enough of this.
We're finished here, brat.
Whoa!
Let him go!
Forge me!
It's that damn kid!
He's got the money, that brat!
Huh?
Ace, you're here!
Thanks for showing up, kid.
You saved us some trouble.
Your friend ain't squealing.
He's pretty tough.
But I think you'll talk. Ace!
Sa-Savo!
Do it!
Boss, are you okay?
Ace!
Sabo!
That kind of hurt.
Who hit me? You?
You punks don't get who
you're messing with.
Yeah, you're all dead me!
Shut your mouth and fight!
Sabo, help Luffy! You guys!
One thing, that ugly dude
has a sword. Be careful.
No way!
Orange of me, that
other kid got our knife!
Quick, make a run for it!
You go ahead.
What?
Ace, let's just leave!
I don't run from my enemies. Ever. Got it?
And I don't go easy on
my enemies. Come on!
These guys aren't just thugs.
They're Blue Jam Pirates!
Yeah, you got that right.
Now, I'm done playing games here.
You've got something that belongs to us.
Be good and give it back you brat
You're just a kid, and I don't
blame you for acting stupid,
but fork over the cash or you'll regret it
We've got better plans for it.
That's our money now
Then you are dead hold on a sec.
I'll be right back
That's enough of this crap
I'm not going to lose, you hear?
I'd rather just kill myself.
Not if we do it first!
Come at me, you pricks!
I heard the whole damn story, Porchemy.
You should be ashamed.
Did you seriously get
beaten by a couple of kids?
Yeah.
Forgive me, Captain.
The money.
I've heard enough of this.
You're not fit for my crew.
Ace, that was really not cool.
Those guys were actual pirates.
Next time, we run.
Whatever your deal is,
it's not worth dying over.
This sucks.
I like my old one better.
We made a huge mistake.
Pissing off pirates like that.
Man, they probably told their captain.
What are we supposed to do now?
That was scary!
I thought I was gonna die!
Would you shut up?
You're not hurt that bad,
so stop crying already!
When are you gonna stop being a baby?
Don't you wanna be a pirate?
Thank you.
You...
You saved me.
Stop it! Calm down.
He's just happy, okay?
All right. What gives?
Why didn't you tell them what they wanted?
You think they wouldn't kill
you because you're a kid?
Those guys don't give a damn.
I was afraid.
I...
but you wouldn't be my
friend. Yeah? Well, so what?
That still beats dying, right?
Besides, why do you want to be my friend?
That's dumb.
Because...
It's not like I've been nice to you.
In fact, I've been giving
you hell ever since we met.
It's been months.
Why haven't you just given up?
Well, cause, cause I, I
got no one else to turn to?
I can't go back to Windmill Village.
I don't like the mountain bandits either.
I'd be all alone all the
time if I didn't follow you!
Getting beat up hurts, but
being lonely hurts more.
Alone? Why?
Gramps is all I have
You feel better around me?
Uh-huh.
Otherwise, you feel lonely? Uh-huh.
Do I think Gold Roger had a kid?
If he did, then too bad for
that poor runt. No kidding.
They'd put him to death.
He'd probably deserve it, too, I bet.
Do you think I deserve to live?
Of course I do!
I see.
But you're still annoying.
Weak little crybabies piss me off.
I'm not weak.
I'm really strong.
Ha!
You think you're really strong?
You were crying your eyes out
the whole time you were tied up.
Have you ever gotten hit
by a spiky thing that big?
I'm just seven years old.
Wait till I turn ten
years old like you guys,
and then I'll be stronger
and won't cry anymore.
Age has nothing to do with it, you brat.
Hell, when I was seven, I was tough.
So what?
I'm gonna be so tough, you're gonna cry.
I promised, Shanks, I'd
be a great pirate someday,
and that means way greater than you.
Ha, you'll be a crappy pirate.
Nuh-uh. Yeah, huh? Nuh-uh.
Okay, enough of that.
Geez.
Now listen, in case you guys forgot,
we got a problem here. A problem?
This forest where I've been living
is awfully close to their hideout,
the Cove of Pirates.
What if one night I'm a little too tired,
sleep a little too hard,
and they sneak up on me?
So, I need your help.
What's with all the bandages?
Have they been fighting
bears or something?
That's not the problem.
Hey, boss, come quick.
This isn't good.
Give me a second, it's early.
Huh?
Ahh!
What have those brats been up to now?
One, two...
Huh?
Hey, Slave, who's that other kid with you?
Who's what now?
Ugh, two brats is already too many!
Who the hell are you?
You mean me?
Ugh, right.
Hi, I'm Sabo.
Huh?
Ace's friend, I see. Oh, good.
It's like I'm already living here.
And you must be Dadan, right?
Hiya!
You're just as worthless as those
other two low-lifes mushing off me.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I heard that you're a
worthless old hag yourself.
Luffy! Ace! Sabo!
There aren't any free rides!
You twerps better be grateful
and get to work this instant!
You got it, thank you!
Fearing for his life, Sabo left Gray
Terminal and found a home with Ace and Luffy,
much to Dedan's dismay.
For the three unwanted guests,
it was a never-ending party.
Making any excuse to get
out of their daily chores,
they hunted wild animals in the mountains,
tussled with hooligans in the city,
and dueled with pirates of the cove.
Within time,
news of their wild exploits
reached far and wide,
even over the high walls surrounding
the center of the kingdom.